Guide to the Robert L. Patten academic papers, 1963-2015 MS 410
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Addenda
  - Subseries J: Dickens Scholarship, Correspondence, and Student Work
    - "Serial Illustrations and Storytelling in David Copperfield" (3/3) (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Dickens, Boz, and the Industrial-Stength Author (1/3) (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Dickens, Boz, and the Industrial-Strength Author (2/3) (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Dickens, Boz, and the Industrial-Strength Author (3/3) (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - "The One and the Many" (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Dickens and Victorian Print Cultures (1/2) (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Dickens and Victorian Print Cultures (2/2) (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: Harvard 19th century British Prose position (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Rosemary Coleman (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Letters for Promotion to Tenure - Alex Regier (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Amelia Scholtz (1/4) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Amelia Scholtz (2/4) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Amelia Scholtz (3/4) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Amelia Scholtz (4/4) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Jennifer Scott (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Victoria Ford Smith (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Jon Varese (1/3) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Jon Varese (2/3) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Jon Varese (3/3) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Jennifer Weeks (1/3) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Jennifer Weeks (2/3) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/Student Work - Jennifer Weeks (3/3) (Restricted) (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence re: The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 1, 2, 3, edited (1/7) (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 4, 5, 6, edited (2/7) (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 7 8, edited (3/7) (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 9, 10, 11, edited (4/7) (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 12, 13, 14, edited (5/7) (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 15 16, edited (6/7) (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - The History of Oxford University Press, Vol. II, Ch. 17 18, edited (7/7) (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence re: Sean Grass, Charles Dickens's Our Mutual Friend... (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - S. Grass, Charles Dickens's Our Mutual Friend - A Pub. Hist., typescript (1/4) (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - S. Grass, Charles Dickens's Our Mutual Friend - A Pub. Hist., typescript (2/4) (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - S. Grass, Charles Dickens's Our Mutual Friend - A Pub. Hist., typescript (3/4) (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - S. Grass, Charles Dickens'sOur Mutual Friend - A Pub. Hist., typescript (4/4) (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Mike Hart (Restricted), 2010 - 2012 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - The New Cultural Marketplace: Victorian Publishing and Reading Practices, Drafts, 2011 - 2013 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Joanna O'Leary (1 of 3) (Restricted), 2008 - 2010 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Joanna O'Leary (2 of 3) (Restricted), 2011 - 2012 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Joanna O'Leary (3 of 3) (Restricted), 2013 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - O'Leary, The Writing Cure, Ch. 1,2,3, 2012 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - O'Leary, The Writing Cure, Ch. 4,5,Bibliography, 2012 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - The Print/Digital Divide, 2005 - 2008, 2010 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Kevin Sigerman, 2010 - 2012 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Woodring Collection Contribution and Research (1 of 2), 2011 - 2013 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Woodring Collection Contribution and Research (2 of 2), 2013 - 2014 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Subseries K: Colleagues/collaborations/recommendations (All files in this subseries are restricted)
    - Baker, James (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Bell, Bill, 1998-2001 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Frost, Simon (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Gadd, Ian, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Golden, Catherine, 2013 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Gould, Marty (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Graham, Sarah, 2007-2011 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Grass, Sean, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Harvey, Margaret, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Hillard, Molly C., 2014 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Kuzmanovic, Dejean, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Miner, Heather, 2007-2014 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Schlicke, Paul, 2009 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Subseries L: Course materials
    - History of the Book in Early Stages of Discipline, Engl 597
      - Introduction, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - Oliver Twist (Box 115, Folder 15)
      - Sketches by Boz (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Oliver Twist, Engl 517, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Oliver Twist, Engl 342, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Subseries M: Dickens scholarship
    - Charles Dickens & the Boz
      - Drafts (Box 115, Folder 19)
      - Typescript (Box 115, Folder 20-21)
      - Paratexts (Box 115, Folder 22)
      - Bibliography (Box 115, Folder 23)
      - Reviews (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - David Copperfield (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Nicholas Nickelby (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Old Curiosity Shop (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Pickwick Papers (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - Dickens (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - "Cradled in Caricature", 2012 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Subseries N: Academic organizations
    - Cambridge Dickens Companion (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Dickens Studies Annual, 2009 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Dickens Universe (Dickens Project)
      - 2004 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - David Copperfield, 2009 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
      - NEH, 2004 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - UCSC, 2012 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - The English Association (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Houston Philosophical Society, 2010 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - New Books on Literature, 2008-2010 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Oxford Authors Companion, 1995-1997 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - SHARP (Society for the History of Authorship, Reading & Publishing), 2009-2013 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Houston Seminar, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Subseries O: Rice-related
    - Fondren Library-Cruikshank Collection, 1999 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Friends of Fondren, 2010 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Student Association, 2009-2010 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Robert Lowrey Patten Awards [Fund], 2010 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Rice Alumni Assn., 2011 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Humanities, 2011 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Sketches for Bob: Papers in Honor of Robert L. Patten, 2012 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Subseries P: Dickens Seminars, Talks, and Publications
    - Centrum New Series, Fall 1981 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - C.D. 2012 Birkbeck Seminar, March 10, 2012 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - C.D. 2012 Free Word, April 2012 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - C.D. 2012 King's College, May 14, 2012 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - C.D. 2012 Syracuse Seminar, May 29-30, 2012 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - C.D. 2012 Little Dorrit talk at Cerisy, May 2012 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - C.D. 2012 Islington (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - C.D. 2012 Charles Dickens Museum (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Centennial, 2012 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Victorian Publishing and Reading Practices, 2016 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - The Dickens World (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Dickens: Unpublished Letters (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Review of English Studies (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Blackwell Encyclopedia of Victorian Literature (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Reader's Report on The Stroller's Tale (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Downtown Abbey (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - The Pickwick Papers (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Dickens Fellowship - Philadelphia (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - George Cruikshank's Life, Times, and Art (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Autobiography into Autobiography: The Evolution of David Copperfield (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Report on "The Trial of John Jasper and The Drood Debate" (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Dickens, Boz, and the Birth of the Industrial-Strength Author (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Book Proposal: Consuming on the Installment Plan (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Cambridge University Press Reviews (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (1) (Box 117, Folder 25)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (2) (Box 117, Folder 26)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (3) (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (4) (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (5) (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (6) (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - C. D. Manuscript with comments (7) (Box 117, Folder 31)